<questionset><question type = "sc"><q>A qualitative variable is</q><feedback> A categorical or qualitative variable is one in which responses are classified according to which category they are in. There is no numeric ranking of the categories.</feedback><choice>	<correct>false</correct>	<ctext>sometimes measured on a continuous scale.</ctext></choice><choice><correct>true</correct>	<ctext>a categorical variable.</ctext></choice><choice><correct>false</correct>	<ctext>a numeric variable.</ctext></choice><randomize>false</randomize></question><question type = "sc"><q>When there are many categories, it is best to use a</q><feedback> Pie charts are not good for displaying many categories. Horizontal bar charts are usually better than vertical bar charts because there is more room to label the categories.</feedback><choice><correct>false</correct>	<ctext> pie chart.</ctext></choice><choice>	<correct>true</correct>	<ctext>horizontal bar chart.</ctext></choice><correct>false</correct><choice>	<ctext> vertical bar chart.</ctext></choice><randomize>false</randomize></question><question type = "sc"><q>When you have relatively few observations you should use percentages rather than frequencies.</q><feedback> Percentages can be misleading when you have relatively few observations. They can make a small difference look large.</feedback><choice>	<correct>false</correct>	<ctext>true</ctext></choice><choice><correct>true</correct>	<ctext>false</ctext></choice><randomize>fale</randomize></question><question type = "sc"><q> A graph with a large lie factor</q><choice><correct>false</correct><ctext>omits data that do not fit the hypothesis.</ctext></choice><choice><correct>false</correct><ctext>is distorted because the baseline is not zero.</ctext></choice><choice><correct>true</correct><ctext>greatly exaggerates differences by comparing areas instead of heights.</ctext></choice><randomize>false</randomize></question><question type = "sc"><q>Three-dimensional bar charts make it easier to interpret the data.</q><choice>	<correct>false</correct>	<ctext>true</ctext></choice><choice><correct>true</correct>	<ctext>false</ctext></choice><feedback> In general, it is a bad idea to have more display dimensions than data dimensions. Three-dimensional bar charts are not as clear as two-dimensional bar charts.</feedback></question></questionset>